quantumbooks.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy for Quantum Bookseller Services

### Our Privacy Policy in a Nutshell

Since opening our doors in 1986, Quantum Bookseller Services has made a commitment to never share the personal information of our customers, for any reason. The personal information you submit to Quantum Bookseller Services online also will never be shared, sold, or disclosed to any third party for any purpose or in any form. 

Quantum Bookseller Services has an opt-in policy concerning commercial email. Should you wish to receive our newsletter or new book information in subject categories you select, you can join our list of subscribers. Otherwise, you will not receive any email from us except for those directly related to any order you place, such as your confirmation and receipt.

Please note that this site contains links to other sites. Quantum Bookseller Services is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### Our Full Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important, so we'd like to explain what information we collect when you visit Quantum Bookseller Services (http://www.quantumbooks.com), why we collect it and how it is used. We'd also like to explain your options to access and control your information, our data security practices and other matters.

THE PRIVACYBOT TRUSTMARK

We have registered with PrivacyBot.com, an independent privacy seal program. We display the PrivacyBot Trustmark to show our commitment to good privacy practices. Click the Trustmark to see our standing with PrivacyBot.

SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN

This Site is not intended for children, especially kids under 13. Children may use this Site only with the direct supervision of their parent.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU? WHY?

We May Profile Users Pseudononymously

We may build a pseudononymous profile of your online habits, interests and activities when you use our Site. This profile will not reveal or be linked to your personal identity. We compile these profiles from user navigation and browsing patterns, and we use these profiles for the purposes described below (please scroll down to each topic for details). 

We May Collect Information Needed to Contact You Later:

If we collect personal contact information (as described below), you may later access it, however, you may not modify or remove it from our system yourself.

We May Collect Your Name, Address and Phone Number. When you use our Site, we may request your name, street address, telephone number or other "real world" contact information. This information may reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents. 

We May Collect Your Email Address. We may request your email address or other information needed to contact you online. This information may reveal who you are or be linked to you personally. We use it to complete and support the immediate activity requested, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents.

We May Collect Other Kinds of Information from You:

When you use our Site, we may collect personal information about you described below. You may not later be able to access, modify or remove the information.

You May be Prompted for a UserID and Password. We may ask you to enter a web site ID, password, or other personal identifier, so we can recognize you. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents. 

We May Collect Purchase Information. We may collect information resulting from a specific purchase you make, such as payment method and credit card numbers, associated with your personal identity. We use this information to complete and support the immediate activity requested, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents. 

We May Collect Navigation and Clickstream Data. As you browse our Site, we may gather navigational and clickstream data that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to build individual profiles for ongoing research, analysis and reporting, and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to our immediate agents.

CERTAIN EXCEPTIONAL DISCLOSURES

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process.

WHAT ARE COOKIES? WHY DO WE USE THEM?

Cookies are small files stored by your browser in your computer when you visit our Site. We use cookies to improve our Site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. We also use cookies to help build a pseudonymous profile of your online habits, interests and activities as you navigate our site, which we use for general research, analysis and reporting. We mostly use "session cookies" that are automatically deleted after each visit. Cookies from our Site can't be read by other sites. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change browser settings to refuse them.

HOW DO WE PROTECT INFORMATION WE COLLECT? 

We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our Site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

HOW LONG DO WE KEEP USER INFORMATION?

We generally keep user data on our server or in our archives for about two (2) years. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely. 

Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within our direct control. Note: we have greater control over recently collected data than for archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, our general data retention policy applies.

YOUR CONSENT TO THIS POLICY

By using our Site, you agree to this Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change it by posting a new version on our Site.

LEGAL DISCLAIMER

THIS SITE OPERATES AS-IS AND AS-AVAILABLE. ANY WARRANTIES OF ACCURACY, QUALITY, TITLE, FITNESS OR MERCHANTABILITY ARE DISCLAIMED. WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, OR FOR EVENTS BEYOND OUR DIRECT CONTROL.

This Policy is governed by Massachusetts law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any provision of this Policy that is illegal or unenforceable shall be deemed automatically conformed to the minimum requirements of law. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Massachusetts within one year after the claim arose, or be barred.

IF YOU HAVE A PRIVACY QUESTION

If you have a privacy question about our Site, please email: William Szabo at [quantum@quantumbooks.com](mailto:quantum@quantumbooks.com). Or write: Quantum Bookseller Services, Attn: William Szabo, Quantum Bookseller Services / Unit 15 355 Middlesex Avenue, Wilmington, MA 01887.

### Privacy Practices Summary 

  * Cookies are used on our site to make the shopping cart work
  * We do not disclose any collected information for any reason 
  * We do not collect any information about 
    * Your Financial History
    * Your PC Configuration
    * How You Use Interactive Features
    * Demographic, Social or Economic Data
    * Your Personal Preferences
    * Your Postings and Online Content
    * Your Political Affiliations
    * Your Health-Related Information
    * Your Social History
  * In the section below 'Why Do We Collect this Information?', we do NOT collect information to: 
    * Run the Site
    * Tele- Marketing
    * Other Marketing
    * Instant Offers
    * Profile R&D

What Do We Collect or Disclose? 

| 

Why Do We Collect this Information?   
  
---|---  
  | 

Collect?

| 

Disclose?

| 

Complete a Request 

| 

Profile Targeting

| 

Customize Content  
  
Your Name, Address, Phone No.

| X |   | 

X

|   |    
  
Your Email Address

| X |   | X |   |    
  
UserID and Password

| X |   | X |   | X  
  
Your Purchases 

| X |   | 

X

|   |    
  
Navigation and Clickstream Data

| X |   |   | X |
